$Generic	Settings
$Enabled 	Enabled
$Timeout	Timeout
$Enables/disables door observer. Exit MCM menu to apply.	Enables/disables door observer. Exit MCM menu to apply.
$Determines how long seconds NPC tries to close a door. If NPC cannot close the door within this period, the door will be left open.	Determines how long seconds NPC tries to close a door. If NPC cannot close the door within this period, the door will be left open.
$Apply to Player	Apply to Player
$Applies this function to player. Doors will be closed when you passed them.	Applies this function to player. Doors will be closed when you passed them.